{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Stained Glass Installation Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/41121/":{"taskOID":41121,"originalTaskOID":41121,"setID":765,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5199,"questionDisplayText":"Installation Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where do you want to install decorative glass? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2339,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Exterior window","answerDisplayText":"Exterior window","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2622,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Framed hanging window","answerDisplayText":"Framed hanging window","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3349,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Interior window","answerDisplayText":"Interior window","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2242,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Entry door insert","answerDisplayText":"Entry door insert","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1215,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Cabinet or bookcase door(s)","answerDisplayText":"Cabinet or bookcase door(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5766,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Skylight","answerDisplayText":"Skylight","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5646,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Shower doors","answerDisplayText":"Shower doors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3859,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Mirror","answerDisplayText":"Mirror","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5200,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Glass","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of glass do you want? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1486,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Colored (stained) glass","answerDisplayText":"Colored (stained) glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3496,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Leaded glass","answerDisplayText":"Leaded glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1636,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Copper foil glass","answerDisplayText":"Copper foil glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1034,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Beveled glass","answerDisplayText":"Beveled glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2257,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Etched glass","answerDisplayText":"Etched glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2693,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Fused glass","answerDisplayText":"Fused glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3363,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Iridescent glass","answerDisplayText":"Iridescent glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5810,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Slumped glass","answerDisplayText":"Slumped glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3298,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Insulated unit (triple-glazed thermo-paned)","answerDisplayText":"Insulated unit (triple-glazed thermo-paned)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17149,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17926,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Overlay glass","answerDisplayText":"Overlay glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5202,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Design","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you know what kind of design you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7163,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes, I have a idea/theme to discuss with designer","answerDisplayText":"Yes, I have a idea/theme to discuss with designer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4240,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No, I need a consultation with designer","answerDisplayText":"No, I need a consultation with designer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5199,"questionDisplayText":"Installation Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where do you want to install decorative glass? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2339,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Exterior window","answerDisplayText":"Exterior window","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2622,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Framed hanging window","answerDisplayText":"Framed hanging window","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3349,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Interior window","answerDisplayText":"Interior window","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2242,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Entry door insert","answerDisplayText":"Entry door insert","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1215,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Cabinet or bookcase door(s)","answerDisplayText":"Cabinet or bookcase door(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5766,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Skylight","answerDisplayText":"Skylight","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5646,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Shower doors","answerDisplayText":"Shower doors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3859,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Mirror","answerDisplayText":"Mirror","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2339,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Exterior window","answerDisplayText":"Exterior window","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2622,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Framed hanging window","answerDisplayText":"Framed hanging window","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3349,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Interior window","answerDisplayText":"Interior window","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2242,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Entry door insert","answerDisplayText":"Entry door insert","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1215,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Cabinet or bookcase door(s)","answerDisplayText":"Cabinet or bookcase door(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5766,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Skylight","answerDisplayText":"Skylight","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5646,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Shower doors","answerDisplayText":"Shower doors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3859,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Mirror","answerDisplayText":"Mirror","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5200,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Glass","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of glass do you want? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1486,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Colored (stained) glass","answerDisplayText":"Colored (stained) glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3496,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Leaded glass","answerDisplayText":"Leaded glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1636,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Copper foil glass","answerDisplayText":"Copper foil glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1034,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Beveled glass","answerDisplayText":"Beveled glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2257,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Etched glass","answerDisplayText":"Etched glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2693,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Fused glass","answerDisplayText":"Fused glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3363,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Iridescent glass","answerDisplayText":"Iridescent glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5810,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Slumped glass","answerDisplayText":"Slumped glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3298,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Insulated unit (triple-glazed thermo-paned)","answerDisplayText":"Insulated unit (triple-glazed thermo-paned)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17149,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17926,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Overlay glass","answerDisplayText":"Overlay glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1486,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Colored (stained) glass","answerDisplayText":"Colored (stained) glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3496,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Leaded glass","answerDisplayText":"Leaded glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1636,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Copper foil glass","answerDisplayText":"Copper foil glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1034,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Beveled glass","answerDisplayText":"Beveled glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2257,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Etched glass","answerDisplayText":"Etched glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2693,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Fused glass","answerDisplayText":"Fused glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3363,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Iridescent glass","answerDisplayText":"Iridescent glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5810,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Slumped glass","answerDisplayText":"Slumped glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3298,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Insulated unit (triple-glazed thermo-paned)","answerDisplayText":"Insulated unit (triple-glazed thermo-paned)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17149,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17926,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Overlay glass","answerDisplayText":"Overlay glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5202,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Design","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you know what kind of design you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7163,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes, I have a idea/theme to discuss with designer","answerDisplayText":"Yes, I have a idea/theme to discuss with designer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4240,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No, I need a consultation with designer","answerDisplayText":"No, I need a consultation with designer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":7163,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes, I have a idea/theme to discuss with designer","answerDisplayText":"Yes, I have a idea/theme to discuss with designer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4240,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No, I need a consultation with designer","answerDisplayText":"No, I need a consultation with designer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/41121/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":41121,"taskName":"Stained or Specialty Glass - Install or Replace","taskDescription":"Create, Install, or Replace Stained or Specialty Glass","xmTaskDescriptor":"Stained Glass Installation Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":232,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Stained Specialty Glass speciality","textMessagingName":"Inst Stain Glass","rolloverLongDesc":"Typically done by an individual artist, stained glasswork involves cutting up many small pieces of colored glass \u0026 securing them between custom shaped metal frames to create an overall picture or image. This also includes staining of glass, etching with chemicals or sand \u0026 other decorative glass effects. Some cabinet \u0026 window manufacturers sell faux stained glass as options. Seek them under the cabinet or window categories.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes stained, etched, leaded \u0026 beveled glass, etc. Does not include repairs.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Create, Install, or Replace Stained or Specialty Glass.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Stained Glass Window Installation \u0026 Replacement \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":73,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Stained / Specialty Glass Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Stained or Specialty Glass - Install or Replace","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Stained Glass Project","urlName":"Stained-or-Specialty-Glass-Install-or-Replace","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Stained Glass Window Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Stained glass, stained, glass, window, specialty glass, speciality window","emcCategoryOid":-12068,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":765,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}